rankyourlisting.com 2012-10-11

# Privacy Notice : RankYourListing, The Ultimate Marketers Toolbox

Company and all its related web sites Privacy Policy PLEASE NOTE: OUR PRIVACY POLICY CHANGES FROM TIME TO TIME AND CHANGES ARE EFFECTIVE UPON POSTING. PLEASE CHECK BACK FREQUENTLY FOR UPDATES AS IT IS YOUR SOLE RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AWARE OF CHANGES. COMPANY DOES NOT PROVIDE NOTICES OF CHANGES IN ANY MANNER OTHER THAN BY POSTING THE CHANGES AT THIS WEB SITE. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE WITH THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY PLEASE DO NOT PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO USE ANY OF THE SERVICES OR PRODUCTS OFFERED OR PROVIDED ON ANY OF THE WEB SITES REFERRED TO IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. The information collection, use, and dissemination practices of company. This policy applies to company’s collection, use, storage and disclosure of information by company on its (a) websites, including all its divisions, subsidiaries, and related companies (collectively, the "Websites"), (b) on various third party websites, and (c) to company’s other information collection, including the purchase of customer lists from third parties. Company is not responsible for the information collection or privacy practices of third party web sites or applications. 

1. Collection of Information. 

1.1 Personal Information. Company collects information from individuals by various methods, including, but not limited to, when an individual voluntarily completes a survey, order form, or a registration page either online or offline, or by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, or registration pages operated by third parties (collectively, a "Survey"). (As used herein, "online" means using the Internet, including the Websites, and related technologies, and "offline" means by methods other than online, including in person, in the postal mail, using telephones and cell phones, and other similar means.) On our websites we may ask an individual to provide various information to company, which may include his or her name, email address, street address, zip code, telephone numbers (including cell phone numbers and carriers), birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and such other information as may be requested from time to time (together, "Personal Information"). Company may also collect information concerning an individual from another source and use that information in combination with information provided from this web site. Completing our online website forms are completely voluntary, and individuals are under no obligation to provide Personal Information to Company, but an individual may receive incentives from company in exchange for providing Personal Information to us. 

1.2 Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Info Collected Using Technology. Company currently uses cookie and web beacon technology to associate certain Internet-related information about an individual with information about the individual in our database. Additionally, Company may use other new and evolving sources of information in the future (together, "Technology Information"). 

(a) Cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of the individual's computer that allows company to identify the individual with his or her corresponding data that resides in company’s database. You may read more about cookies at http://cookiecentral.com. Individuals who use the Websites need to accept cookies in order to use all of the features and functionality of the Websites. 

(b) New Technology. The use of technology on the Internet, including cookies and web beacons, is rapidly evolving, as is company’s use of new and evolving technology. As a result, company strongly encourages individuals to revisit this policy for any updates regarding its use of technology. 

1.3 Outside Information. Company may receive information about individuals from third parties or from other sources of information outside of company including information located in public databases ("Outside Information"). 

1.4 Individual Information. As used herein, Individual Information means Personal Information, Third Party List Information, Other Information, Technology Information, and Outside Information, and any other information Company gathers or receives about individuals. 

1.5 No Information Collected from Children. Company will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because it does not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third parties. Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

1.6 Credit Card Information. Company may in certain cases collect credit card numbers and related information, such as the expiration date of the card ("Credit Card Information") when an individual places an order from Company. When the Credit Card Information is submitted to Company, such information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. Company will use the Credit Card Information for purposes of processing and completing the purchase transaction, and the Credit Card Information will be disclosed to third parties only as necessary to complete the purchase transaction. 

2. Use of Individual Information. 

2.1 Discretion to Use Information. THE COMPANY MAY USE INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION FOR ANY LEGALLY PERMISSIBLE PURPOSE IN COMPANY'S SOLE DISCRETION. The following paragraphs in Section 2 describe how Company currently uses Individual Information, but Company may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, Company may update this policy from time to time. Company may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, SMS Text Messages (Cellular) and package stuffers, among other possible uses. If you do not wish for us to use personal information about you to promote or sell our products and services or to sell, transfer or otherwise provide personal information about you to third parties, please inform us by contacting customer service and we will certainly honor your request. You can stop all communication anytime by unsubscribing from our lists using the unsubscribe links in our email messages or by writing to STOP RankYourListing Messages: PO Box 50192, Myrtle Beach, SC 29579 or simply send an email correspondence to info@rankyourlisting.com 

2.2 Email. Company uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. Company may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list or by sending an email correspondence to info@rankyourlisting.com 

2.2(a) Content of Email Messages. In certain commercial email messages sent by Company, an advertiser's name will appear in the "From:" line but hitting the "Reply" button will cause a reply email to be sent to Company. The "Subject:" line of Company email messages will usually contain a line provided from the advertiser to Company. 

2.2(b) Solicited Email. Company only sends email to individuals who have agreed on the Websites to receive email from Company or to individuals who have agreed on third party websites to receive email from third parties such as Company. Company does not send unsolicited email messages. As a result, statutes requiring certain formatting for unsolicited email are not applicable to Company email messages. All email solicitations will be in full compliance with the CAN SPAM Act of 2003.

2.3 Targeted Advertising. Company uses Individual Information to target advertising to an individual. When an individual is using the Internet, Company uses Technology Information (see also Section 2.5 below) to associate an individual with that person's Individual Information, and Company attempts to show advertising for products and services in which the person has expressed an interest in the Surveys, etc., or indicated an interest by means of Technology Information, and otherwise. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising by using email, direct mail, telephones, cell phones, and other means of communication to provide promotional offers. 

2.4 Direct Mail and Telemarketing. Company uses Individual Information to advertise, directly or indirectly, to individuals using direct mail marketing or telemarketing using telephones and cell phones. 

2.5 Use of Technology Information. Company uses Technology Information (1) to match a person's Personal Information and Third Party List Information to other categories of Individual Information to make and improve profiles of individuals, (2) to track a person's online browsing habits on the Internet, (3) to determine which areas of Company web sites are most frequently visited. This information helps Company to better understand the online habits of individuals so that Company can target advertising and promotions to them. 

2.6 Profiles of Individuals. Company uses Individual Information to make a profile of an individual. A profile can be created by combining Personal Information and Third Party List Information with other sources of Individual Information such as information obtained from public databases. 

2.7 Storage of Individual Information. Company does NOT store Credit card information. Company stores the Individual Information in a database on Company computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under Company control. Notwithstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Company computers from being illegally accessed, and the Individual Information on them stolen or altered.

2.8 Use of Data Collected

We use your personal, demographic, and profile data to enhance your experience at our site and to enable us to present content we think you might be interested in. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic, and profile data to improve our site, for statistical analysis, for marketing and promotional purposes, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future telemarketing, SMS text-messaging, e-mails, or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. By using this site, you agree that you may be contacted in any manner contemplated in this section even if your number is found on a do not call registry, in-house list, or similar registry. 

2.9 Opt-out rights (Cellular Phone) You may remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you. You may remove your information by  sending  "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. You may also send your request to us via postal mail: STOP RankYourListing Messages: PO Box 50192, Myrtle Beach, SC 29579 or simply send an email correspondence to info@rankyourlisting.com

3. Dissemination of Individual Information. 

3.1 Order Fulfillment. Company will transfer Individual Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a person orders from such third party while using Company web sites or when responding to offers provided by Company. 

3.2 Legal Process. Company may disclose Individual Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders, and other legal processes.

3.3 Access. Individuals have access to their Individual Information collected to provide an opportunity for an individual to correct, amend, or delete such information. Access can be obtained by contacting customer service. Company may also grant advertising clients and email services providers access to an individual's email address to verify the origin of the Individual Information collected. 

4. Privacy Practices of Third Parties. 

4.1 Advertiser cookies and web beacons. Advertising agencies, advertising networks, and other companies (together, "Advertisers") who place advertisements on the Websites and on the Internet generally may use their own cookies, web beacons, and other technology to collect information about individuals. Company does not control Advertisers' use of such technology and Company has no responsibility for the use of such technology to gather information about individuals. 

4.2 Links. The Websites and email messages sometimes contain hypertext links to the web sites of third parties. Company is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites. Linked web sites may contain links to web sites maintained by third parties. Such links are provided for your convenience and reference only. Company does not operate or control in any respect any information, software, products or services available on such third party web sites. The inclusion of a link to a web site does not imply any endorsement of the services or the site, its contents, or its sponsoring organization. 

4.3 Affiliated Companies. Company may disclose, transfer, and sell Individual Information to entities affiliated with Company in Company’s discretion. 

5. Unsubscribe Procedures. If you wish to discontinue receiving email messages from Company please contact customer service or unsubscribe from our email messages.

We reserve the right to add Individual Information to multiple lists maintained by Company. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov if you have questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us at: STOP RankYourListing Messages: PO Box 50192, Myrtle Beach, SC 29579 or simply send an email correspondence to info@rankyourlisting.com
